[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":64273,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":153534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":10126,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":163661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":13622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":177284,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1881,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":179165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":7627,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":186793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1247,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":188041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the seco nd one t o it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":14744,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":202785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":913,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":203699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6813,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":210513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":857,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":211371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4649,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":216021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub> 6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":835,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":216857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":219469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":817,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":220287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br />< br /> (R emember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":224287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":863,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":225151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":228075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":4335,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":232411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":235339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":839,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":236179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":238202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":813,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":239015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":18230,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":257247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse  under +< sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":45318,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":302567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":11225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":313793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":915,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":314709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Reme mber, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2418,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":317127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":883,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":318011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":319653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":848,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":320501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2147,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":322648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub> 6</sub>. ","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":323608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":327171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6675,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":333847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be per formed s tarting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":19634,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":353481,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but  there i s no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":159810,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":513291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":16129,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":529421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":10173,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":539595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br />< br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":544127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":186264,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":730391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under  +<sub>6 </sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":734961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":33598,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":768559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":6884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":775443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":7263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":782707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We' ll give  you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":23679,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":806387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":810959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":971,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":811930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":815807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":819539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":9472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":829011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4044,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":833055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":835823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":120273,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":956097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4+1 = 5 and 5 is less than 9 so the answer remains the same.","explanation_history":["41","4+1 = 5 and 5 is less than 9 so the answer remains the same."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":27958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":984055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4= 12 and 12 is higher than 9 so 12-9=3.","explanation_history":["8 +","8 ","8+4 ","8+4= 12 and 12-9","8+4= 12 and 12-","8+4= 12 and 12 is higher than 9 so 12-9=3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":26681,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1010737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"answers are between 0 and 8.","explain":true,"explanation":"You start with a first number then add a second one to it.  If the sum is smaller than a 9, then that's the result.  If the sum is 9 or bigger than subtract 9 from it to get the result.","explanation_history":["You start witha first number then add a se","You start with a first number then add a second one to it.  If the sum is smaller than a 9, then that's the result.  If the sum is 9 or bigger than subtract 9 from it to get the result."],"response_history":["answers ","answers","answers between 0 and 8.","answers abetween 0 and 8.","answers arebetween 0 and 8.","answers are between 0 and 8."],"rt":146382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1157119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":43645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1200765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1202923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":42563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1245487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"6+3=9 and it's equal to 9 - 9 = 0.  So it's an inverse under +9.","explanation_history":["6 + ","6 +","6 ","6+3 ","6+3= ","6+3=9 and it's equal to 9 0 ","6+3=9 and it's equal to 9 0","6+3=9 and it's equal to 9 - 9 = 0.  So it's an inverse.","6+3=9 and it's equal to 9 - 9 = 0.  So it's an inverse under +9."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":40028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1285515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 using just 2.","explanation_history":["There's no way of making 1,2,","There's no way of making 1,2","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 under ","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 under","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 unde","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 und","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 un","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 u","There's no way of making 1,3,5,7 using just 2."],"response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":194859,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1480375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"3 can make every other element under +9.","explanation_history":["t","the nu","the n","the ","the","th","t","3 can make every other element  under +9  ","3 can make every other element under +9."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":41120,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1521495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"5 can't make every other element under +9.","explanation_history":["5 can't make any other element under +9.","5 can't make e other element under +9.","5 can't make ebv other element under +9.","5 can't make eb other element under +9.","5 can't make ev other element under +9.","5 can't make ever other element under +9.","5 can't make every other element under +9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":36901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1558396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator und er +<sub >9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"6=6, and no way to name 1 under +9.","explanation_history":["6=6, 0            ","6=6, 0           ","6=6, 0          ","6=6, 0         ","6=6, 0        ","6=6, 0       ","6=6, 0      ","6=6, 0     ","6=6, 0    ","6=6, 0   ","6=6, 0  ","6=6, 0 ","6=6, 0","6=6, ","6=6, and no way to name 1 under +9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":113293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1671691,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessar y.","rt":21990,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1693681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +_n x = 0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0 = 1 _","0 = 1 + ","0 = 1 +","0 = 1 ","0 = 1","0 = ","0 =","0 ","0","n = ","n =","n -1","n - -1 ","n - -1","n - -","n - ","n -","n ","n + 1 = 0","n - 1 = 0","n - )1","n - )","n - )","n - (1+","1 +_n x = 0"],"rt":252201,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1945882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n = x + y ","explain":true,"explanation":"You would get t he diffe rence between n and x to find the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, the total is 0. ","explanation_history":["You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y.  ","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subtract ","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subtract","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subtrac","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subtra","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subtr","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then subt","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then sub","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then su","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then s","You would get the difference between n and  x to fi nd the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, th","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, the su","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, the s","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, the total o","You would get the difference between n and x to find the value of y. Then if the sum of x + y are subtracted from n, the total is 0. "],"response_history":["x + ","x +","x ","x","n = x + y = 0","n = x + y "],"rt":123328,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2069211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Odd numbers can't be generated by even numbers.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Odd numbers can't be generated by even numbers,","Odd numbers can't be generated by even numbers."],"rt":26419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2095630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16867,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2112498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Tr ue","Fal se"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":6378,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2118877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":6070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2124947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"It's easier to generate values under n if x is a multiple of n.","explanation_history":["It's easier to generate values under n using ","It's easier to generate values under n using","It's easier to generate values under n usin","It's easier to generate values under n usi","It's easier to generate values under n us","It's easier to generate values under n u","It's easier to generate values under n if x is a multiple of n."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":50193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2175141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":8796,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2183937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"Guess.","explanation_history":["n/a","Guess."],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":21534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2205471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":27088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2232559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1748,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2234307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"35","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["35"],"rt":3244,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2237551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no deg ree","Ma sters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2239957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"differential equations","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["differential clacu","differential clac","differential cla","differential cl","differential c","differential eu","differential equations"],"rt":15968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2255925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of mod ular ari thmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":11530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2267455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":5355,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2272811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2277780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2824,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2280605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2284387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":1728,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2286115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2290790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2296685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  It was too short and couldn't really get a good grasp of it.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I felt  the concept of number generator s could' ve been explained more in more deat","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more dea","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I felt","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I fel","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I fe","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I f","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I ","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  I","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  It was too short and couldn't really gr","I felt  the concept of number generators could've been explained more in more detail.  It was too short and couldn't really get a good grasp of it."],"rt":38606,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2335291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]